First off, welcome to Las Vegas. My my
question for you is just what was your
kind of like interaction like with the
Raiders um throughout the pre-draft
process?
>> Um the interaction it was smooth, you
know, we had a couple zones, talked with
um the quarterback coach, man. We just
had a couple interaction and they went
good.
>> Sorry Sam, go ahead.
>> Hey, um welcome to Las Vegas. You had 18
pass breakups last season. And can you
just talk about the ball skills that you
have and what you can bring to this
secondary?
>> Oh yeah, man. I just feel like my IQ and
my instincts when I'm out there on the
field, it just unmatched. So ended up
last season with 18 pass deflections
>> as a guy. Just to follow up on that a
little bit, you know, what changed for
you at Cal because you were productive
when you were at FIU, but at Cal
obviously took it to another level
there.
>> Um, I just say that off seasonason, man,
I just got bigger, stronger, and faster,
man. So, I just feel like when I was out
on the field, that would just help me
improve my game my last year.
>> Hi, Heidi Fang, Las Vegas Review
Journal, excuse me. Just wondering when
you look at the defense that the Raiders
are starting to put together, how much
does that excite you?
>> That excite me on well, man. You know,
we a couple young guys, but we coming
in, you know, they brought me in, I'm
coming to change the program around.
you you talked about the you know going
to going to Cal last year and getting
stronger. Um how much did it do for your
confidence knowing that you could play
at that level and step up to the level
that you did last year and still be able
to perform?
>> Um yeah man I just say man coming in in
January man I just want to say thanks to
coach Novak man. So he had a um plan for
me and then we executed the plan and I
just really like really got bigger like
it's playing.
>> Yeah. Welcome to Las Vegas. Uh on top of
that, is there is there any other
coaches that you could think of either
at FIU or even at Cal that you feel
contributed to you being able to take
that leap your senior year?
>> Oh yeah, for sure. Definitely coach Alan
Brown. Really, I think I was fortunate
throughout my whole college career. I
had nothing but great coaches. Like
everyone taught me something different.
So I just say thanks to all my coaches
who coached me.
Congratulations, Hezekiah, on seeing
your NFL dream come true. We started
writing back on February 9th.
>> Yes, sir. We started writing on February
9th about the Raiders interest in you.
So, you've had some time to
>> watch this relationship percolate a
little bit and think about this as a
possibility. What does it mean to you
now to be officially a Raider and be
part of the Silver and Black,
>> man? You know, man, you know, Raiders,
man, just crazy, man. Just the franchise
history, man. Raiders just excellent
foundation, man. So, it just so real,
you know, just growing up, I always
wanted to be in the NFL, and I finally
here, so I'm not taking it lightly, you
know, just all gas, no burgers.
>> All right, we're going to wrap it up
with Sam. Go ahead.
>> Uh, you didn't cross paths with Fernando
Mendoza at Cal, but I assume you had a
lot of teammates that played with him
there. Um, I was wondering if you picked
anything up from them on what he's like
as a player and as a person.
Oh yeah man. Yeah definitely. You know
they had talks on the locker room. Well
around the locker room they just say you
know Fern Fernando just a great guy and
just he always himself you know he be
himself and then great leadership.
>> Awesome. Thanks so much Hezekiah. I
appreciate you.
>> Yes ma'am. Thank you. Thank y'all.